{
    "Items": [
		{
			"question": "2 + 1 = ?",
			"correctAns": "3",
			"wrongAns": ["5", "6", "1"]
		},
		{
			"question": "2 + 3 = ?",
			"correctAns": "5",
			"wrongAns": ["10", "8", "6"]
		},
		{
			"question": "5 + 2 = ?",
			"correctAns": "7",
			"wrongAns": ["2", "8", "10" ]
		},
		{
			"question": "3 + 1 = ?",
			"correctAns": "4",
			"wrongAns": ["2", "5", "7"]
		},
		{
			"question": "6 + 2 = ?",
			"correctAns": "8",
			"wrongAns": ["2", "3", "5"]
		},
		{
			"question": "8 + 4 = ?",
			"correctAns": "12",
			"wrongAns": ["9", "1", "5"]
		},
		{
			"question": "9 + 2 = ?",
			"correctAns": "11",
			"wrongAns": ["8", "9", "7"]
		},
		{
			"question": "5 + 4 = ?",
			"correctAns": "9",
			"wrongAns": ["4", "5", "7"]
		},
		{
			"question": "1 + 6 = ?",
			"correctAns": "7",
			"wrongAns": ["3", "8", "5"]
		},
		{
			"question": "9 + 6 = ?",
			"correctAns": "15",
			"wrongAns": ["21", "14", "25"]
		},
		{
			"question": "9 + 11 = ?",
			"correctAns": "20",
			"wrongAns": ["25", "13", "34"]
		},
		{
			"question": "5 + 8 = ?",
			"correctAns": "13",
			"wrongAns": ["10", "12", "16"]
		},
		{
			"question": "10 + 2 = ?",
			"correctAns": "12",
			"wrongAns": ["20", "10", "2"]
		},
		{
			"question": "8 + 1 = ?",
			"correctAns": "9",
			"wrongAns": ["10", "5", "2"]
		}
    ]
}